[Caine]: [distorted scream]
Guys, I set up a musical adventure for you today!
But the song starts at 12:30,
and I didn't have time to write lyrics!
You'll have to make up the lyrics on the spot,
or suffer a horrible punishment!
[Pomni]: What punishment?!
[Caine]: 12:30!
[Pomni]: [screams]
I c-- I can't sing without a script!
[Caine]:Hup!
[Pomni]:This is a shampoo bottle!
[Caine]:The song, Pomni!
[Pomni]: [stammers]
[sung to tune of "I Am The Very Model"]
♪ Contains citric acid, sodium chloride ♪
♪ Cocamidopropyl betaine, fumic acid ♪
♪ Butylphenyl, methylpropional, uh ♪
♪ Magnesium nitrate, PEG-60 almond glycerides ♪
[Bubble]: Sounds delicious!
[Pomni]: ♪ Methylchloroisothiazolinone ♪
And, uh, water!
[Gangle]: ♪ I'm super happy, never sappy ♪
♪ When I have my have my happy mask ♪
♪ Don't break it, Jax!
Don't break it, Jax! ♪
♪ Don't break it, Jax! That's all I ask! ♪
[glass shatters]
What the [HOOOONK]???
Kinger!!!
[Kinger]: Oop, sorry.
Just... [chomps]
eatin' a little banana.
[Ragatha]: ♪ Sunny days and rainbows,
getting hugs and petting kitty cats ♪
♪ When you feel down and in the mud
instead of frowning ♪
Do a silly dance!
Take it away, Zooble.
[Zooble]: This is stupid.
[Caine]: Boo! Come on!
Let loose those angelic pipes, Zooble!
[Zooble]: AAAAAGH!
[Jax]: ♪ Zooble's part was terrible
that act was so unbearable ♪
♪ I'm super duper hoping that
those limbs are not repairable ♪
[chuckles] AUGH!
[jazzy remix of "Digital Circus" theme plays]
[Kinger]: [jazzy voice]
♪ Y'all know me as Kinger ♪
♪ But on the stage, I'm Singer ♪
♪ Gonna serenade ya, baby ♪
♪ With my own
Tony-winning zingeeeeeeeers ♪
Ow.
[Caine]: Alright, Pomni.
Let's bring this hootenanny home
with a classic duet!
[Pomni]: Gummigoo??
[Gummigoo]: Crikey!
[Pomni]: [gasps] Gummigoo!
Oh, my gosh!
I can't believe you're alive!
[Gummigoo]: Crikey!
[Pomni]: W-Wha...?
[glitched audio]
Crikey -- Down under --
[Pomni]: AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
[Caine]: AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
[Bubble]: AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHH
[Caine]: AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHH
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
[Pomni]: AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHH!!!
[Caine]: Congratulations!
You completed your musical adventure!
As your punishment, I am going to...
[booming, echoing voice]
MASS PRODUCE YOU.
[Pomni]:
Wait, we're still being punished?!
[Caine]: [normal voice]
That's the thing about life, Pomni.
Sometimes, you get...
[booming, echoing voice]
MASS PRODUCED.
[normal voice]
These scrumdiddlyumptious bumpkins
could be yours today!
Along with this delicious sticker pack
featuring all your favorite characters
as sweet, teeth-rotting treats!
Your friend, the Gummigoo keychain,
in all his NON-EDIBLE glory.
Perfect for NOT EATING.
And this complete pin line,
pinning all your favorite characters
in a line together
as their completely pinnable selves
in this completely pinnable complete pin line!
[Jax]: And me, Jax,
the marketable vinyl figure.
[chuckles] What can I say?
People paying money to just admire me all day
sounded like a sweet gig.
[Caine]: Right you are, Jax,
the marketable vinyl figure!
Him and all these items are available now
at digitalcircus.store
That’s...